# shahrzad khoobyari

San Anselmo, CA Shkoobyari@gmail.com 2065518341

Registered Pharmacist in California and Washington with 10+ years' work experience, seeking the opportunity to utilize a skill set that features a strong attention to detail, great problem-solving ability and interpersonal skills in cross-cultural environments to help improve a professional and passionate organization.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

## Work Experience

#### **Clinical Pharmacist**

Gateway Pharmacy Psychiatric Specialty Pharmacy/Staffing Agency - Fairfield, CA June 2019 to Present

- Reviewed completed prescription orders ensuring proper product dispensing
- Checked medications for content, accuracy and completeness of all drug packaging and labeling to provide final verification of prescription

Counseled patients regarding the proper use of prescription and over-the-counter medications

- Consulted and advised health care providers regarding medication therapy
- Trained individuals in how to use devices to promote optimal medical support
- Researched customer health insurance plans to provide prescription authorization and efficient patient care
- Discussed over-the-counter medication and equipment options to help patients deal with individual symptoms

#### **Clinical Pharmacist**

San Dimos Hospital and Pharmacy Specialty - San Dimas, CA July 2017 to February 2018

- Utilize CPOE to record, review and analyze patient's updated medical information daily in preparation for general medicine dispensing.
- Utilize institutionally based guidelines to appropriately dose psychotherapy medications, anticoagulation treatment, vancomycin, amino glycosides, antibiotics, chemotherapeutic agents and TPN.
- Consulted and advised health care providers regarding medication therapy
- Supervise staff in picking and packing medication and medical supplies with a focus on order fulfillment accuracy.
- Medication reconciliation on admission and patients' counseling on discharge
- Utilize CPOE to communicate and document clinical information.
- Worked with the Omnicell and Cerner.
- Utilize medication for Blue and Stroke Code. Monthly assignment of monitoring crash carts.
- Utilized weekly ADR and monthly DUR for Pharmacy and Therapeutic committee.
- Familiarize self with current new pharmaceutical preparations prescribed for utilization by patients to be able to render assistance to patients

• Support pharmacy services in line with state and federal requirements and implement enhancement of quality for the department

#### **Clinical Pharmacist**

Ca State Psychiatric Facility/ Staffing Agency - Corcoran, CA January 2017 to June 2017

- Record, review and analyze patients updated medical information daily for general medicine dispensing
- Worked with EMR systems such as Cerner.
- · Worked with the Omnicell.
- Consulted and advised health care providers regarding medication therapy
- Supervise staff in picking and packing medication with a focus on order fulfillment accuracy
- Utilize clinical based guidelines to properly dose psychotherapy medications, anticoagulation, aminoglycoside and antibiotics
- Medication reconciliation on admission and patients' counseling on discharge
- Support pharmacy services in line with State and federal requirements
- Monthly assignment of unit inspection

#### **Clinical Pharmacist**

Telepharmacy - Roseville, CA May 2015 to May 2016

- Utilize Cerner to record, review and analyze patient's updated medical information daily in preparation for general medicine dispensing of five Hospitals in California and one hospital in Washington
- Utilize institutionally based guidelines to appropriately dose psychotherapy medications, anticoagulation treatment, vancomycin, amino glycosides, antibiotics and TPN
- Consulted and advised health care providers regarding medication therapy
- Utilize CPOE to communicate and document clinical information. Worked with the Omnicell
- Medication reconciliation on admission and patients' counseling on discharge
- Attend monthly interdepartmental meetings regarding contemporary therapeutic topics

#### **Clinical Pharmacist**

Feather River Hospital - Paradise, CA August 2010 to May 2015

- Utilize Cerner to record, review and analyze patient's updated medical information daily in preparation for general medicine dispensing.
- Utilize institutionally based guidelines to appropriately dose anticoagulation treatment, vancomycin, amino glycosides, chemotherapeutic agents and TPN.
- Supervise staff in picking and packing medication and medical supplies with a focus on order fulfillment accuracy.
- Utilize CPOE to communicate and document clinical information
- · Worked with the Omnicell
- Medication reconciliation on admission and patients' counseling on discharge
- Utilize medication for Code Blue, Monthly crash carts inspections
- Attend Stroke Code
- Utilized weekly ADR and monthly DUR for Pharmacy and Therapeutic committee.

#### **Clinical Pharmacist**

Walgreens Home Infusion - Chico, CA May 2009 to May 2011

- Provided concise and timely response to requests for drug information from health care providers and patient
- Designed, recommended, monitored and evaluated patient-specific pharmacy care plans for Pharmacotherapy of patient
- Utilize institutionally based guidelines to appropriately dose anticoagulation treatment, vancomycin, amino glycosides, other antibiotics, Blood Factors, TPN and Enteral nutrition, chemotherapeutic and immunotherapy agents
- Worked with various infusion pump and experienced in programing, training patients and troubleshooting
- Educated and experienced with various IV line and their maintenance
- Recommended modification in the prescribed medication therapy or monitoring parameters of patient's care

#### **Clinical Pharmacist**

Walgreens Home Infusion - Chico, CA April 2010 to April 2011

- Reviewed completed prescription orders ensuring proper product dispensing
- Checked medications for content, accuracy and completeness of all drug packaging and labeling to provide final verification of prescription
- Counseled patients regarding the proper use of prescription and over-the-counter medications
- Consulted and advised health care providers regarding medication therapy
- Administered vaccines to immunize patients against communicable diseases
- Trained individuals in how to use devices to promote optimal medical support
- Researched customer health insurance plans to provide prescription authorization and efficient patient care
- Discussed over-the-counter medication and equipment options to help patients deal with individual symptoms

### Education

### **Doctor of Pharmacy in Pharmacy**

Tehran University, College of Pharmacy and Health Sciences - Tehran, IR

#### Skills

- Worked in various Hospital and retail settings, LTC and Specialty Pharmacy including Walgreens and Gateway Psychiatric Pharmacy. (10+ years)
- Trained and worked with Cerner, Meditech, Epic, Pharmnet, Omnicell and Pyxis.
- Trained and Experienced in compounding oral and topical medications (5 years)
- Anti-coagulation, (10+ years)
- Adult, Pediatric and Infant TPN/ETN (10+ years)
- Antibiotic Stewardship (MAD-ID) (5 years)
- Immunization (Certified) (2 years)
- Chemotherapy (In process of Obtaining Board Certification)
- Parenteral Specialty Therapy Such as IVTG, Monoclonal agents (10+ years)

- Pain management, Palliative care and Hospice (10+ years)
- MTM (Certified), Medication reconciliation and counseling patients. (4 years)
- Trained and worked with CPR PLUS Software for Home Infusion and Pharmacy Specialty (2 years)
- Hospital (10+ years)
- Oncology (5 years)
- Prior Authorization (2 years)
- Order Fulfillment (10+ years)
- EMR Systems (10+ years)
- Medication Administration
- Critical Care Experience (10+ years)
- Compounding Medications (4 years)
- Order Entry (10+ years)
- Clinical Pharmacy Experience (10+ years)
- Pharmacy Technician Experience
- Leadership
- ICU Experience (10+ years)
- Laboratory Experience
- Medical Records

### Certifications and Licenses

# **Registered Pharmacist**

### **Licensed Pharmacist**